    public class LocationExportData
    {
        public int Id { get; set; }
        public string Code { get; set; } = \
\;
        public string Name { get; set; } = \\;
        public string Description { get; set; } = \\;
        public int MaxCapacity { get; set; }
        public int CurrentCapacity { get; set; }
        public int AvailableCapacity { get; set; }
        public double UtilizationPercentage { get; set; }
        public bool IsActive { get; set; }
        public bool IsFull { get; set; }
        public string CapacityStatus { get; set; } = \\;
        public DateTime CreatedDate { get; set; }
        public DateTime? ModifiedDate { get; set; }
        public string CreatedBy { get; set; } = \\;
    }

    #endregion
